[
  {
    "Question": "to be (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich bin",
    "ParentId": 1,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:45:39.6685728+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to be (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du bist",
    "ParentId": 1,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:21:18.6390186+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to be (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er ist",
    "ParentId": 1,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:22:35.7028776+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to be (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr seid",
    "ParentId": 1,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:47:18.1484395+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to be (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich war",
    "ParentId": 1,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:43:41.8526281+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to be (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du warst",
    "ParentId": 1,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:23:49.1267832+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to be (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er war",
    "ParentId": 1,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:20:37.8551782+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to be (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wart",
    "ParentId": 1,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:43:38.3486865+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to call, to shout (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich rufe",
    "ParentId": 4,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:38:36.9620884+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to call, to shout (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du rufst",
    "ParentId": 4,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:47:14.4842833+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to call, to shout (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er ruft",
    "ParentId": 4,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:33:56.1065679+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to call, to shout (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr ruft",
    "ParentId": 4,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:46:15.196416+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to call, to shout (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich rief",
    "ParentId": 4,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:34:26.1224882+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to call, to shout (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du riefst",
    "ParentId": 4,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:52:39.6034336+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to call, to shout (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er rief",
    "ParentId": 4,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:56:33.0743793+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to call, to shout (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr rieft",
    "ParentId": 4,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:45:19.3965736+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to sing (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich singe",
    "ParentId": 7,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:42:27.092885+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to sing (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du singst",
    "ParentId": 7,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:45:24.5644631+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to sing (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er singt",
    "ParentId": 7,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:43:55.3646126+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to sing (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr singt",
    "ParentId": 7,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:20:24.3590534+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to sing (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich sang",
    "ParentId": 7,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:45:46.1964159+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to sing (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du sangst",
    "ParentId": 7,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:38:41.5860446+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to sing (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er sang",
    "ParentId": 7,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:52.5301437+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to sing (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr sangt",
    "ParentId": 7,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:58:09.8583029+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to dance (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich tanze",
    "ParentId": 10,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:26.8423223+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to dance (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du tanzt",
    "ParentId": 10,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:45:27.8684543+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to dance (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er tanzt",
    "ParentId": 10,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:46.7861472+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to dance (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr tanzt",
    "ParentId": 10,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:28:09.6012225+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to dance (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich tanzte",
    "ParentId": 10,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:41.4900971+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to dance (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du tanztest",
    "ParentId": 10,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:54:23.1867118+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to dance (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er tanzte",
    "ParentId": 10,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:45:03.8128678+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to dance (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr tanztet",
    "ParentId": 10,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:36:16.594434+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to lie (on the floor) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich liege",
    "ParentId": 13,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:22:04.647+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to lie (on the floor) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du liegst",
    "ParentId": 13,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:21:54.0388679+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to lie (on the floor) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er liegt",
    "ParentId": 13,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:20:58.7591221+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to lie (on the floor) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr liegt",
    "ParentId": 13,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:56:43.7306667+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to lie (on the floor) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich lag",
    "ParentId": 13,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:38:33.1860629+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to lie (on the floor) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du lagst",
    "ParentId": 13,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:53:58.3227446+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to lie (on the floor) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er lag",
    "ParentId": 13,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:21:57.8549931+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to lie (on the floor) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr lagt",
    "ParentId": 13,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:34:38.9304347+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to have (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich habe",
    "ParentId": 16,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:39:14.9619907+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to have (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du hast",
    "ParentId": 16,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:59:31.0421799+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to have (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er hat",
    "ParentId": 16,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:35:14.450379+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to have (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr habt",
    "ParentId": 16,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:44.2181233+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to have (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich hatte",
    "ParentId": 16,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:29.546222+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to have (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du hattest",
    "ParentId": 16,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:30:33.0009719+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to have (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er hatte",
    "ParentId": 16,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:44:19.0286787+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to have (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr hattet",
    "ParentId": 16,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:22:29.7348735+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to think (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich denke",
    "ParentId": 19,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:20:44.1459455+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to think (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du denkst",
    "ParentId": 19,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:46:24.196332+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to think (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er denkt",
    "ParentId": 19,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:39:03.1619936+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to think (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr denkt",
    "ParentId": 19,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:22:11.6868674+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to think (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich dachte",
    "ParentId": 19,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:24.14618+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to think (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du dachtest",
    "ParentId": 19,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:11.098311+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to think (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er dachte",
    "ParentId": 19,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:55.8741387+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to think (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr dachtet",
    "ParentId": 19,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:21:50.1988742+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to die (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich sterbe",
    "ParentId": 22,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:49.4581095+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to die (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du stirbst",
    "ParentId": 22,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:46:45.0763283+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to die (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er stirbt",
    "ParentId": 22,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:38:50.1700445+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to die (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr sterbt",
    "ParentId": 22,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:39:00.5300403+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to die (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich starb",
    "ParentId": 22,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:22:42.310923+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to die (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du starbst",
    "ParentId": 22,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:22:24.4468474+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to die (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er starb",
    "ParentId": 22,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:42:57.7887372+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to die (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr starbt",
    "ParentId": 22,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:57:24.9623849+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to live (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich lebe",
    "ParentId": 25,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:46:11.3484357+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to live (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du lebst",
    "ParentId": 25,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:14.266234+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to live (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er lebt",
    "ParentId": 25,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:46:37.2843638+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to live (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr lebt",
    "ParentId": 25,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:42:20.4847752+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to live (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich lebte",
    "ParentId": 25,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:38:45.5380118+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to live (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du lebtest",
    "ParentId": 25,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:55:29.522599+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to live (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er lebte",
    "ParentId": 25,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:36:59.7782129+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to live (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr lebtet",
    "ParentId": 25,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:38:04.9942139+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to see (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich sehe",
    "ParentId": 28,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:43:46.7006874+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to see (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du siehst",
    "ParentId": 28,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:44:29.0445597+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to see (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er sieht",
    "ParentId": 28,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:45:36.3166085+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to see (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr seht",
    "ParentId": 28,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:35:57.2103351+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to see (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich sah",
    "ParentId": 28,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:47:23.3563964+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to see (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du sahst",
    "ParentId": 28,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:34:29.8265668+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to see (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er sah",
    "ParentId": 28,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:38:11.9540786+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to see (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr saht",
    "ParentId": 28,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:20:48.3830901+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to fetch, to get (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich hole",
    "ParentId": 166,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:05.2822546+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to fetch, to get (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du holst",
    "ParentId": 166,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:44:08.3325962+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to fetch, to get (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er holt",
    "ParentId": 166,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:48:00.1322354+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to fetch, to get (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr holt",
    "ParentId": 166,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:36:29.7382676+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to fetch, to get (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich holte",
    "ParentId": 166,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:44:58.4444878+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to fetch, to get (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du holtest",
    "ParentId": 166,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:20:28.4232047+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to fetch, to get (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er holte",
    "ParentId": 166,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:36:09.5463116+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to fetch, to get (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr holtet",
    "ParentId": 166,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:45:58.1884194+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to learn (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich lerne",
    "ParentId": 205,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:22:33.1269125+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to learn (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du lernst",
    "ParentId": 205,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:47:46.9164456+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to learn (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er lernt",
    "ParentId": 205,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:39:12.3379974+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to learn (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr lernt",
    "ParentId": 205,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:20:21.0631793+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to learn (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich lernte",
    "ParentId": 205,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:39:09.5380297+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to learn (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du lerntest",
    "ParentId": 205,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:21:02.3033621+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to learn (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er lernte",
    "ParentId": 205,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:35:21.2823979+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to learn (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr lerntet",
    "ParentId": 205,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:35:01.8504159+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "country (singular)",
    "Answer": "das Land",
    "ParentId": 2,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:36:55.442237+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "country (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Länder",
    "ParentId": 2,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:20:31.5989826+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "world (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Welt",
    "ParentId": 5,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:42:37.2687483+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "world (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Welten",
    "ParentId": 5,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:22:01.2708513+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "human (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Mensch",
    "ParentId": 8,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:58.8341515+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "human (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Menschen",
    "ParentId": 8,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:21:21.5270059+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "road, street (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Straße",
    "ParentId": 11,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:36:49.1382423+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "road, street (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Straßen",
    "ParentId": 11,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:33:42.4746289+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ache, pain (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Schmerz",
    "ParentId": 14,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:35:34.8423636+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ache, pain (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Schmerzen",
    "ParentId": 14,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:21:05.6710679+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "hand (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Hand",
    "ParentId": 17,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:57:57.3543207+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "hand (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Hände",
    "ParentId": 17,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:34:08.2504872+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "sparrow (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Spatz",
    "ParentId": 20,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:46:48.6283059+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "sparrow (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Spatzen",
    "ParentId": 20,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:38:53.1460868+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "parent (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Eltern",
    "ParentId": 23,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:42:54.2447502+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "water (singular)",
    "Answer": "das Wasser",
    "ParentId": 26,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:38:14.9861036+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "alternative (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Alternative",
    "ParentId": 29,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:46:28.0523523+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "alternative (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Alternativen",
    "ParentId": 29,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:36:45.4662592+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "number (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Nummer",
    "ParentId": 32,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:33:46.3465434+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "number (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Nummern",
    "ParentId": 32,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:45:07.3884987+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "telephone (singular)",
    "Answer": "das Telefon",
    "ParentId": 35,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:52:53.4428824+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "telephone (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Telefone",
    "ParentId": 35,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:39:06.2419944+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "phone number (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Telefonnummer",
    "ParentId": 38,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:31:33.314907+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "phone number (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Telefonnummern",
    "ParentId": 38,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:34:04.362551+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "night (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Nacht",
    "ParentId": 41,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:38:56.3060683+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "night (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Nächte",
    "ParentId": 41,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:34:34.1704535+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "school (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Schule",
    "ParentId": 44,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:43:49.9966408+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "school (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Schulen",
    "ParentId": 44,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:43:59.3486078+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kitchen (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Küche",
    "ParentId": 47,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:31:18.32424+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "kitchen (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Küchen",
    "ParentId": 47,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:36:35.3543953+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "father (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Vater",
    "ParentId": 50,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:45:10.8764761+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "father (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Väter",
    "ParentId": 50,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:21.3861698+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "table (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Tisch",
    "ParentId": 53,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:46:06.5803939+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "table (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Tische",
    "ParentId": 53,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:38:17.6420888+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "morning (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Morgen",
    "ParentId": 56,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:44:12.996655+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "morning (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Morgen",
    "ParentId": 56,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:34:12.53056+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "newspaper (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Zeitung",
    "ParentId": 59,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:20:10.1197451+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "newspaper (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Zeitungen",
    "ParentId": 59,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:38:08.4661294+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mother (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Mutter",
    "ParentId": 62,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:21:08.7749623+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "mother (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Mütter",
    "ParentId": 62,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:31:37.7308028+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "bun, roll (singular)",
    "Answer": "das Brötchen",
    "ParentId": 65,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:22:39.102815+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "bun, roll (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Brötchen",
    "ParentId": 65,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:41:43.5891578+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jam (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Marmelade",
    "ParentId": 68,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:29:31.7370379+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "jam (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Marmeladen",
    "ParentId": 68,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:20:41.6551178+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "cinnamon bun (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Zimtschnecke",
    "ParentId": 71,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:46:58.7004023+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "cinnamon bun (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Zimtschnecken",
    "ParentId": 71,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:20:16.9431343+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "cereal (singular)",
    "Answer": "das Müsli",
    "ParentId": 74,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:38.9141852+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "milk (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Milch",
    "ParentId": 77,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:35:30.0503547+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "banana (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Banane",
    "ParentId": 80,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:38:23.1860981+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "banana (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Bananen",
    "ParentId": 80,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:35:45.8023282+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "slice (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Scheibe",
    "ParentId": 83,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:30:37.1529535+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "slice (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Scheiben",
    "ParentId": 83,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:48:03.6523207+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "bread (singular)",
    "Answer": "das Brot",
    "ParentId": 86,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:46:34.244509+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "bread (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Brote",
    "ParentId": 86,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:35.714156+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "ham (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Schinken",
    "ParentId": 89,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:47:50.1084971+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "cheese (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Käse",
    "ParentId": 92,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:35:38.4583306+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "butter (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Butter",
    "ParentId": 95,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:54:06.130753+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "apple (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Apfel",
    "ParentId": 98,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:33:50.9226438+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "apple (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Äpfel",
    "ParentId": 98,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:22:07.6709892+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "sausage (singular)",
    "Answer": "die Wurst",
    "ParentId": 101,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:35:10.5704739+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "sausage (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Würste",
    "ParentId": 101,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:36:05.842488+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "honey (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Honig",
    "ParentId": 104,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:29:19.705027+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "egg (singular)",
    "Answer": "das Ei",
    "ParentId": 107,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:43:01.444715+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "egg (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Eier",
    "ParentId": 107,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:47:06.5564108+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "coffee (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Kaffee",
    "ParentId": 110,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:47:02.8684341+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "tea (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Tee",
    "ParentId": 113,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:45:14.5964971+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "juice (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Saft",
    "ParentId": 116,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:20:55.0151482+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "juice (plural)",
    "Answer": "die Säfte",
    "ParentId": 116,
    "Type": 12,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:20:34.4710501+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "yoghurt (singular)",
    "Answer": "der Joghurt",
    "ParentId": 119,
    "Type": 11,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:35:42.4183716+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "whole (positive)",
    "Answer": "ganz",
    "ParentId": 3,
    "Type": 13,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:45:33.1724763+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "happy (positive)",
    "Answer": "glücklich",
    "ParentId": 6,
    "Type": 13,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:32.6741308+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "happy (comparative)",
    "Answer": "glücklicher",
    "ParentId": 6,
    "Type": 14,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:35:06.9543959+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "happy (superlative)",
    "Answer": "am glücklichsten",
    "ParentId": 6,
    "Type": 15,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:36:40.7142564+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "cold (positive)",
    "Answer": "kalt",
    "ParentId": 9,
    "Type": 13,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:45:42.9327181+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "cold (comparative)",
    "Answer": "kälter",
    "ParentId": 9,
    "Type": 14,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:47:11.8283201+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "cold (superlative)",
    "Answer": "am kältesten",
    "ParentId": 9,
    "Type": 15,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:34:21.1464859+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "young (positive)",
    "Answer": "jung",
    "ParentId": 12,
    "Type": 13,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:46:20.4283986+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "young (comparative)",
    "Answer": "jünger",
    "ParentId": 12,
    "Type": 14,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:47:27.3404024+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "young (superlative)",
    "Answer": "am jüngsten",
    "ParentId": 12,
    "Type": 15,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:22:20.7829467+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "big (positive)",
    "Answer": "groß",
    "ParentId": 15,
    "Type": 13,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:36:19.8743582+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "big (comparative)",
    "Answer": "größer",
    "ParentId": 15,
    "Type": 14,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:37:18.4262199+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "big (superlative)",
    "Answer": "am größten",
    "ParentId": 15,
    "Type": 15,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:38:20.6581062+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "warm (positive)",
    "Answer": "warm",
    "ParentId": 18,
    "Type": 13,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T18:20:51.247107+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "warm (comparative)",
    "Answer": "wärmer",
    "ParentId": 18,
    "Type": 14,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:46:03.4204253+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "warm (superlative)",
    "Answer": "am wärmsten",
    "ParentId": 18,
    "Type": 15,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:59:39.402151+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "calm, quiet (positive)",
    "Answer": "ruhig",
    "ParentId": 21,
    "Type": 13,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:36:52.6182008+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "calm, quiet (comparative)",
    "Answer": "ruhiger",
    "ParentId": 21,
    "Type": 14,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:35:26.5225173+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "calm, quiet (superlative)",
    "Answer": "am ruhigsten",
    "ParentId": 21,
    "Type": 15,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:47:57.0682613+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brief, short (positive)",
    "Answer": "kurz",
    "ParentId": 24,
    "Type": 13,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:28:34.569252+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brief, short (comparative)",
    "Answer": "kürzer",
    "ParentId": 24,
    "Type": 14,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T17:34:48.1705082+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "4.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "brief, short (superlative)",
    "Answer": "am kürzesten",
    "ParentId": 24,
    "Type": 15,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:53:10.5949174+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to ask (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich frage",
    "ParentId": 31,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:52:27.9987832+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to ask (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du fragst",
    "ParentId": 31,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:58:42.6690132+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to ask (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er fragt",
    "ParentId": 31,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:05:28.3070313+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to ask (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr fragt",
    "ParentId": 31,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:08:01.5144847+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to ask (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich fragte",
    "ParentId": 31,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:54:41.9971947+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to ask (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du fragtest",
    "ParentId": 31,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:06:39.0667414+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to ask (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er fragte",
    "ParentId": 31,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:07:19.8506394+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to ask (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr fragtet",
    "ParentId": 31,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:57:50.3892297+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to reply, to answer (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich antworte",
    "ParentId": 34,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:58:55.8128902+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to reply, to answer (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du antwortest",
    "ParentId": 34,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:59:00.3651666+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to reply, to answer (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er antwortet",
    "ParentId": 34,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T22:57:04.2122917+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to reply, to answer (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr antwortet",
    "ParentId": 34,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:00:03.9805862+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to reply, to answer (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich antwortete",
    "ParentId": 34,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:59:31.2047727+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to reply, to answer (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du antwortetest",
    "ParentId": 34,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T22:57:39.7563076+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to reply, to answer (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er antwortete",
    "ParentId": 34,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:08:25.8422815+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to reply, to answer (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr antwortetet",
    "ParentId": 34,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:50:40.8717558+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to take (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich nehme",
    "ParentId": 37,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:31:35.7966073+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to take (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du nimmst",
    "ParentId": 37,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:04:47.4272406+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to take (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er nimmt",
    "ParentId": 37,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:52:44.4786474+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to take (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr nehmt",
    "ParentId": 37,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:59:12.0209209+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to take (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich nahm",
    "ParentId": 37,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:58:21.9171498+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to take (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du nahmst",
    "ParentId": 37,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:54:26.3581028+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to take (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er nahm",
    "ParentId": 37,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:03:34.3556079+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to take (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr nahmt",
    "ParentId": 37,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T20:00:05.850117+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to sleep (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich schlafe",
    "ParentId": 40,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:56:35.5255898+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to sleep (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du schläfst",
    "ParentId": 40,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:06:09.8429579+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to sleep (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er schläft",
    "ParentId": 40,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:51:28.5910318+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to sleep (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr schlaft",
    "ParentId": 40,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:05:23.9150816+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to sleep (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich schlief",
    "ParentId": 40,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:08:14.9543521+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to sleep (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du schliefst",
    "ParentId": 40,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:55:00.9091249+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to sleep (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er schlief",
    "ParentId": 40,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:57:54.1222785+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to sleep (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr schlieft",
    "ParentId": 40,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:03:23.0517489+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to want (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich will",
    "ParentId": 43,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:32:44.2045919+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to want (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du willst",
    "ParentId": 43,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:52:22.6948041+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to want (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er will",
    "ParentId": 43,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:04:58.9072137+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to want (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wollt",
    "ParentId": 43,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T22:56:42.8765418+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to want (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich wollte",
    "ParentId": 43,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:05:59.2669409+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to want (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du wolltest",
    "ParentId": 43,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:57:24.4773729+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to want (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er wollte",
    "ParentId": 43,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:58:14.9811665+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to want (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wolltet",
    "ParentId": 43,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:29:59.9170808+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to must (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich muss",
    "ParentId": 46,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:32:05.9484956+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to must (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du musst",
    "ParentId": 46,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:56:55.1254769+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to must (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er muss",
    "ParentId": 46,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:51:05.5832096+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to must (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr müsst",
    "ParentId": 46,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:57:18.7093951+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to must (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich musste",
    "ParentId": 46,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:50:48.1591935+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to must (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du musstest",
    "ParentId": 46,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:05:37.1230605+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to must (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er musste",
    "ParentId": 46,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:08:56.1380948+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to must (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr musstet",
    "ParentId": 46,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:07:34.2985149+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to can (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich kann",
    "ParentId": 49,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:05:49.7469585+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to can (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du kannst",
    "ParentId": 49,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:06:45.5548283+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to can (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er kann",
    "ParentId": 49,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:53:22.7504573+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to can (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr könnt",
    "ParentId": 49,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:51:23.167129+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to can (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich konnte",
    "ParentId": 49,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:32:37.6923535+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to can (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du konntest",
    "ParentId": 49,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:59:44.3726749+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to can (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er konnte",
    "ParentId": 49,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:33:26.5161345+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to can (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr konntet",
    "ParentId": 49,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:08:09.0422896+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to be called (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich heiße",
    "ParentId": 52,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:05:04.7391974+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to be called (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du heißt",
    "ParentId": 52,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:55:01.2939948+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to be called (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er heißt",
    "ParentId": 52,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:35:29.6915306+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to be called (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr heißt",
    "ParentId": 52,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:57:41.6613194+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to be called (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich hieß",
    "ParentId": 52,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:55:12.2370896+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to be called (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du hießt",
    "ParentId": 52,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:54:31.8613049+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to be called (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er hieß",
    "ParentId": 52,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:59:34.4581514+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to be called (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr hießt",
    "ParentId": 52,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:02:55.3158565+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to come (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich komme",
    "ParentId": 55,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:58:33.7890853+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to come (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du kommst",
    "ParentId": 55,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:30:18.2289738+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to come (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er kommt",
    "ParentId": 55,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:29:43.8134545+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to come (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr kommt",
    "ParentId": 55,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:56:50.7415154+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to come (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich kam",
    "ParentId": 55,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:06:04.5708888+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to come (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du kamst",
    "ParentId": 55,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:57:40.5222643+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to come (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er kam",
    "ParentId": 55,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T20:55:04.1570857+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to come (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr kamt",
    "ParentId": 55,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T19:57:55.7095737+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to live, to stay (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich wohne",
    "ParentId": 58,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:54:02.5068678+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to live, to stay (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du wohnst",
    "ParentId": 58,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:55:21.7466396+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to live, to stay (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er wohnt",
    "ParentId": 58,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:01:23.7713064+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to live, to stay (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wohnt",
    "ParentId": 58,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:55:50.9784613+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to live, to stay (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich wohnte",
    "ParentId": 58,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:57:30.6503576+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to live, to stay (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du wohntest",
    "ParentId": 58,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:52:59.1308629+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to live, to stay (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er wohnte",
    "ParentId": 58,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:59:22.9141948+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to live, to stay (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wohntet",
    "ParentId": 58,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:05:48.106072+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to speak (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich spreche",
    "ParentId": 61,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:55:25.0905703+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to speak (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du sprichst",
    "ParentId": 61,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:53:32.122799+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to speak (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er spricht",
    "ParentId": 61,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:56:38.73047+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to speak (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr sprecht",
    "ParentId": 61,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:01:14.9153789+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to speak (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich sprach",
    "ParentId": 61,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T20:00:09.026091+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to speak (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du sprachst",
    "ParentId": 61,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:03:40.1626904+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to speak (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er sprach",
    "ParentId": 61,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:57:20.3223996+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to speak (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr spracht",
    "ParentId": 61,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:01:39.3552546+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to understand (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich verstehe",
    "ParentId": 64,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:05:07.6902944+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to understand (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du verstehst",
    "ParentId": 64,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:58:13.6103284+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to understand (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er versteht",
    "ParentId": 64,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:56:53.0504658+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to understand (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr versteht",
    "ParentId": 64,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:54:47.4826326+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to understand (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich verstand",
    "ParentId": 64,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:59:53.2981742+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to understand (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du verstandst",
    "ParentId": 64,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:55:12.8026575+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to understand (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er verstand",
    "ParentId": 64,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:54:15.9068707+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to understand (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr verstandet",
    "ParentId": 64,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:53:41.6108167+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to mean (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich bedeute",
    "ParentId": 67,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:03:56.7145731+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to mean (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du bedeutest",
    "ParentId": 67,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:57:07.4104588+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to mean (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er bedeutet",
    "ParentId": 67,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:13:34.1279499+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to mean (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr bedeutet",
    "ParentId": 67,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:55:56.0025676+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to mean (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich bedeutete",
    "ParentId": 67,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:57:00.2265707+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to mean (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du bedeutetest",
    "ParentId": 67,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:12:29.6563108+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to mean (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er bedeutete",
    "ParentId": 67,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:13:21.7360239+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to mean (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr bedeutetet",
    "ParentId": 67,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T22:57:47.3724947+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to know (starts with w) (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich weiß",
    "ParentId": 70,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:05:28.3702647+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to know (starts with w) (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du weißt",
    "ParentId": 70,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:04:51.5464087+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to know (starts with w) (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er weiß",
    "ParentId": 70,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:01:34.2033054+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to know (starts with w) (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wisst",
    "ParentId": 70,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T22:56:50.2203232+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to know (starts with w) (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich wusste",
    "ParentId": 70,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:53:05.162743+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to know (starts with w) (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du wusstest",
    "ParentId": 70,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:13:49.1757839+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to know (starts with w) (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er wusste",
    "ParentId": 70,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:03:26.3150537+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to know (starts with w) (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wusstet",
    "ParentId": 70,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:15:11.1114627+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to make, to do (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich mache",
    "ParentId": 73,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:04:55.7223472+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to make, to do (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du machst",
    "ParentId": 73,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:05:41.5221003+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to make, to do (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er macht",
    "ParentId": 73,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:57:10.9384043+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to make, to do (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr macht",
    "ParentId": 73,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:01:07.9959871+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to make, to do (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich machte",
    "ParentId": 73,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:12:41.5442992+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to make, to do (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du machtest",
    "ParentId": 73,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:04:01.4746012+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to make, to do (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er machte",
    "ParentId": 73,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:59:26.0261269+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to make, to do (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr machtet",
    "ParentId": 73,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:53:17.2267769+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to need (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich brauche",
    "ParentId": 76,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:05:37.8101298+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to need (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du brauchst",
    "ParentId": 76,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:58:45.2502137+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to need (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er braucht",
    "ParentId": 76,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:54:27.4349331+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to need (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr braucht",
    "ParentId": 76,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:13:41.5759082+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to need (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich brauchte",
    "ParentId": 76,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:52:44.9228659+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to need (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du brauchtest",
    "ParentId": 76,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:13:45.047864+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to need (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er brauchte",
    "ParentId": 76,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:59:48.9941302+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to need (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr brauchtet",
    "ParentId": 76,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T22:57:23.6362708+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to eat (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich esse",
    "ParentId": 79,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:03:47.8026269+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to eat (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du isst",
    "ParentId": 79,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:07:47.5938253+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to eat (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er isst",
    "ParentId": 79,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:54:09.8186239+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to eat (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr esst",
    "ParentId": 79,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:01:28.2353064+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to eat (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich aß",
    "ParentId": 79,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:03:52.3547977+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to eat (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du aßest",
    "ParentId": 79,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:03:31.3547009+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to eat (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er aß",
    "ParentId": 79,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:56:00.3224208+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to eat (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr aßt",
    "ParentId": 79,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:59:58.7541515+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to should (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich soll",
    "ParentId": 82,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:05:34.5061349+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to should (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du sollst",
    "ParentId": 82,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:59:17.9061565+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to should (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er soll",
    "ParentId": 82,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:53:21.7867785+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to should (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr sollt",
    "ParentId": 82,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:57:44.4823822+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to should (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich sollte",
    "ParentId": 82,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-27T21:02:05.8670991+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to should (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du solltest",
    "ParentId": 82,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:58:00.5302244+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to should (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er sollte",
    "ParentId": 82,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:54:30.4026442+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to should (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr solltet",
    "ParentId": 82,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T19:59:45.6181021+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to address informally with du (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich duze",
    "ParentId": 85,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:31:49.5848221+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to address informally with du (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du duzt",
    "ParentId": 85,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:20:21.1064814+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to address informally with du (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er duzt",
    "ParentId": 85,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:31:28.6088682+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to address informally with du (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr duzt",
    "ParentId": 85,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:28:44.2651744+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to address informally with du (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich duzte",
    "ParentId": 85,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:31:40.8968192+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to address informally with du (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du duztest",
    "ParentId": 85,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:31:13.9448448+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to address informally with du (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er duzte",
    "ParentId": 85,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:30:11.5449963+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to address informally with du (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr duztet",
    "ParentId": 85,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:22:45.9617199+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to address formally with Sie (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich sieze",
    "ParentId": 88,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:31:17.8729263+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to address formally with Sie (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du siezt",
    "ParentId": 88,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:25:57.5213729+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to address formally with Sie (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er siezt",
    "ParentId": 88,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:23:03.3696834+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to address formally with Sie (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr siezt",
    "ParentId": 88,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:31:02.704936+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to address formally with Sie (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich siezte",
    "ParentId": 88,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:24:51.0654863+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to address formally with Sie (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du sieztest",
    "ParentId": 88,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:24:43.0016201+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to address formally with Sie (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er siezte",
    "ParentId": 88,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:20:32.0419008+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to address formally with Sie (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr sieztet",
    "ParentId": 88,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:24:31.3375385+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to may (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich darf",
    "ParentId": 91,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:21:48.5060312+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to may (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du darfst",
    "ParentId": 91,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:24:23.6736053+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to may (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er darf",
    "ParentId": 91,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:21:22.601938+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to may (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr dürft",
    "ParentId": 91,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:25:12.7855093+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to may (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich durfte",
    "ParentId": 91,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:26:54.3292719+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to may (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du durftest",
    "ParentId": 91,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:27:55.3612669+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to may (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er durfte",
    "ParentId": 91,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:23:22.0337203+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to may (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr durftet",
    "ParentId": 91,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:30:04.4809614+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to awake, to wake up (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich wache auf",
    "ParentId": 94,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:31:45.0808516+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to awake, to wake up (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du wachst auf",
    "ParentId": 94,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:21:40.809819+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to awake, to wake up (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er wacht auf",
    "ParentId": 94,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:30:27.2249103+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to awake, to wake up (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wacht auf",
    "ParentId": 94,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:31:35.1848083+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to awake, to wake up (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich wachte auf",
    "ParentId": 94,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:29:16.9130007+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to awake, to wake up (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du wachtest auf",
    "ParentId": 94,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:30:57.5288589+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to awake, to wake up (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er wachte auf",
    "ParentId": 94,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:27:49.5691527+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to awake, to wake up (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr wachtet auf",
    "ParentId": 94,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:28:15.2891207+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to rise, to get up (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich stehe auf",
    "ParentId": 97,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:21:07.5538607+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to rise, to get up (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du stehst auf",
    "ParentId": 97,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:23:15.553674+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to rise, to get up (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er steht auf",
    "ParentId": 97,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:29:01.5530587+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to rise, to get up (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr steht auf",
    "ParentId": 97,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:26:47.2653529+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to rise, to get up (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich stand auf",
    "ParentId": 97,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:23:51.3857594+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to rise, to get up (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du standst auf",
    "ParentId": 97,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:22:28.2337823+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to rise, to get up (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er stand auf",
    "ParentId": 97,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:21:28.6578568+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to rise, to get up (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr standet auf",
    "ParentId": 97,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-28T23:25:21.0334456+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to have breakfast (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich frühstücke",
    "ParentId": 100,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:54:01.2517016+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to have breakfast (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du frühstückst",
    "ParentId": 100,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:57:26.8512722+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to have breakfast (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er frühstückt",
    "ParentId": 100,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:55:03.5235246+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to have breakfast (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr frühstückt",
    "ParentId": 100,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:52:37.3238339+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to have breakfast (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich frühstückte",
    "ParentId": 100,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:57:21.3233182+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to have breakfast (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du frühstücktest",
    "ParentId": 100,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:55:16.7075139+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to have breakfast (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er frühstückte",
    "ParentId": 100,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:52:02.55623+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to have breakfast (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr frühstücktet",
    "ParentId": 100,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:56:24.4833757+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to start, to begin (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich beginne",
    "ParentId": 103,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:53:11.9397488+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to start, to begin (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du beginnst",
    "ParentId": 103,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:54:11.8915625+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to start, to begin (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er beginnt",
    "ParentId": 103,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:54:08.7155965+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to start, to begin (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr beginnt",
    "ParentId": 103,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:52:26.7077769+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to start, to begin (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich begann",
    "ParentId": 103,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:53:15.6916918+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to start, to begin (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du begannst",
    "ParentId": 103,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:52:44.4677262+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to start, to begin (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er begann",
    "ParentId": 103,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:52:49.7798603+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to start, to begin (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr begannt",
    "ParentId": 103,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:54:53.9315576+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to go, to walk (Präsens, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich gehe",
    "ParentId": 106,
    "Type": 0,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:54:15.1235633+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to go, to walk (Präsens, du)",
    "Answer": "du gehst",
    "ParentId": 106,
    "Type": 1,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:53:06.7237805+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to go, to walk (Präsens, er)",
    "Answer": "er geht",
    "ParentId": 106,
    "Type": 2,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:52:17.9158325+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to go, to walk (Präsens, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr geht",
    "ParentId": 106,
    "Type": 4,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:52:22.8197699+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to go, to walk (Präteritum, ich)",
    "Answer": "ich ging",
    "ParentId": 106,
    "Type": 5,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:53:56.3956539+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to go, to walk (Präteritum, du)",
    "Answer": "du gingst",
    "ParentId": 106,
    "Type": 6,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:55:41.7794779+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to go, to walk (Präteritum, er)",
    "Answer": "er ging",
    "ParentId": 106,
    "Type": 7,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:56:41.1714447+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "1.00:00:00"
  },
  {
    "Question": "to go, to walk (Präteritum, ihr)",
    "Answer": "ihr gingt",
    "ParentId": 106,
    "Type": 9,
    "LastTrainingTime": "2022-03-29T01:53:23.5396784+02:00",
    "Cooldown": "2.00:00:00"
  }
]